export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Who discovered the wreckage of the Titanic?",
    optionA: "D. Michael Harris",
    optionB: "Jack Grimm",
    optionC: "Robert Ballard",
    optionD: "George Tulloch",
    correctOption: "optionC"},

{
  question: "How long after the execution of Anne Boleyn did Henry VIII marry Jane Seymour?",
  optionA: "11 days",
  optionB: "21 days",
  optionC: "11 months",
  optionD: "11 years",
  correctOption: "optionA"},
  // options: ["11 days", "21 days", "11 months", "11 years"],
  // correctOption: "11 days"},

{
  question: "British Summer Time begins on the last Sunday in which month?",
  optionA: "February",
  optionB: "March",
  optionC: "April",
  optionD: "May",
  correctOption: "optionB"},
  // options: ["February", "March", "April", "May"],
  // correctOption: "March"}

{
  question: "What does the Welsh word 'sglodion' mean in English?",
  optionA: "Chips",
  optionB: "Tea",
  optionC: "Cardigan",
  optionD: "Coins",
  correctOption: "optionA"},
//   options: ["Chips", "Tea", "Cardigan", "Coins"],
//   correctOption: "Chips"},

{
  question: "Street artist Banksy is originally associated with which British city?",
  optionA: "London",
  optionB: "Sheffield",
  optionC: "Bristol",
  optionD: "Bath",
  correctOption: "optionC"},
  // options: ["London", "Sheffield", "Bristol", "Bath"],
  // correctOption: "Bristol"},

{
  question: "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
  optionA: "Auckland",
  optionB: "Hamilton",
  optionC: "Queenstown",
  optionD: "Wellington",
  correctOption: "optionD"},
  // options: ["Auckland", "Hamilton", "Queenstown", "Wellington"],
  // correctOption: "Wellington"},

{
  question: "Which London Underground line has the most stations?",
  optionA: "Northern Line",
  optionB: "Central Line",
  optionC: "Jubilee Line",
  optionD: "District Line",
  correctOption: "optionD"},
  // options: ["Northern Line", "Central Line", "Jubilee Line", "District Line"],
  // correctOption: "District Line"},

{
  question: "English astronomer John Couch Adams discovered which planet in 1846?",
  optionA: "Jupiter",
  optionB: "Saturn",
  optionC: "Pluto",
  optionD: "Neptune",
  correctOption: "optionD"},

{
  question: "From what grain is the Japanese spirit Sake made?",
  optionA: "Rice",
  optionB: "Cucumber",
  optionC: "Potato",
  optionD: "Barley",
  correctOption: "optionA"},

{
  question: "What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2019?",
  optionA: "Julia",
  optionB: "Olivia",
  optionC: "Rachel",
  optionD: "Amy",
  correctOption: "optionB"},

{
  question: "How many permanent teeth does a dog have?",
  optionA: "40",
  optionB: "42",
  optionC: "44",
  optionD: "46",
  correctOption: "optionB"},

{
  question: "In what year did The Beatles split up?",
  optionA: "1966",
  optionB: "1968",
  optionC: "1970",
  optionD: "1972",
  correctOption: "optionC"},

{
  question: "How many horses are on each team in a polo match?",
  optionA: "4",
  optionB: "5",
  optionC: "6",
  optionD: "2",
  correctOption: "optionA"},

{
  question: "Which colour pill does Neo swallow in The Matrix?",
  optionA: "White",
  optionB: "Blue",
  optionC: "Red",
  optionD: "Yellow",
  correctOption: "optionC"},

{
  question: "Gouda is a popular cheese originating from which country?",
  optionA: "Germany",
  optionB: "France",
  optionC: "Finland",
  optionD: "Netherlands",
  correctOption: "optionD"},

{
  question: "How many notes are there in a musical scale?",
  optionA: "5",
  optionB: "6",
  optionC: "7",
  optionD: "8",
  correctOption: "optionC"},

{
  question: "What’s the name of the talking snowman in Disney’s Frozen?",
  optionA: "Olaf",
  optionB: "Yeti",
  optionC: "Frosty",
  optionD: "Josh",
  correctOption: "optionA"},

{
  question: "What is the best-selling novel of all time?",
  optionA: "Harry Potter",
  optionB: "Don Quixote",
  optionC: "The Hobbit",
  optionD: "The Little Prince",
  correctOption: "optionB"}

]